Adam Kovacevich

5193 Peachtree Blvd Apartment 1130, Chamblee, GA 30341. E-Mail: Akovacevich11@gmail.com Tel: +1(269)-760-6886

Mission:

Although I have little web-design experience from the past, I have just now begun unlocking my full potential in Full-Stack Web Development. From Front-End to Back-End; I am coding my very own beautiful, fully responsive websites and mobile applications. My goal is to become a full-stack web developer with a heavy focus on iOS and Android mobile applications development. I eagerly look forward to helping you deploy the perfect applications to help your business and clients succeed.

Experience:

• Interior Development Group, Inc. (December 2017-Present)

- My roles at this company include: Business Development, Marketing, Design, Engineering and Fabrication of aircraft interior components and fixtures. Additionally, I assist in managing aircraft completion projects across multiple departments.
- I also designed and developed the company's website. <u>www.idgjets.com</u>.

• CharterPad, Inc. (March 2016 - June 2016) Director of Business Development

- Generated partnerships and new customer accounts with a nationwide network of FAA Part-135 Air Carriers. Assisted with the integration of vendor aircraft scheduling software, Rockwell Collins FOS and other software to CharterPad's software suite and database. This helped increase CharterPad's product offering by enabling access to hundreds of additional flights.
- CharterPad is an aircraft charter brokerage web and mobile application which enables aircraft charter brokers and management companies to view a real-time market of available FAA Part 135 aircraft.

• Bizjet Mobile, LLC (Previously "ExecJet Mobile") (October 2013 – March, 2016)

- Vice President of Sales & Business Development
- Wireless router manufacturer & Satellite Airtime Data Provider. Products included an Iridium Satcom System and a separate router which interfaced with existing Inmarsat SwiftBroadband SDUs.
- Managed sales team and develops sales strategies for worldwide aircraft crew and passenger communication systems which operate on the Iridium and Inmarsat Satellite Networks.
 Performed aircraft / avionics review and testing for pre-sale and post-sale analysis for Fortune 500 clients and high net-worth individuals' aircraft. Oversee pre and post installation phases, training of crew and owner/operators on the products.
- Developed and negotiated mutually beneficial business relationships and client relationships with FAA Part 145, Part 135, Part 91 and Part 121 certificate holders, owners and operators.
- Developed technical sales and marketing documentation, materials and resources. Managed and represented the company at industry trade shows, conferences and individual client relations meetings. Negotiated and closed with customers and maintenance/installation facilities for the sale and installation of systems. Supervised the successful installation of

systems on client's aircraft. Performed technical and operational demonstrations of systems and software.

• Iridium & Inmarsat Satellite Communications Service Provider

• Advanced Aircraft Parts, LLC

(April, 2014- Sept 2014)

- Co-Owner / Operator and Chief Executive Officer
- Partnership between myself and 2 business partners for buying/reselling used aircraft parts, avionics, airframes and engines to the global marketplace.
- Solely directing Purchasing, Sales, Marketing and Administrative Duties

• ExecJet Mobile, LLC.

(July, 2013- May, 2014)

- See BizJetMobile -
- ExecJet Mobile, LLC. was reorganized as BizjetMobile, LLC.
- Iridium & Inmarsat Satellite Communications Service Provider

• Planetary Grid Wireless, LLC.

(2012- Present)

- Deputy Chief Technical Officer & Managing Member
- Assisting the Chief Technical Officer, Chairman and other Company Officers in developing Iridium based M2M satellite communications technologies for vertical market segments.
- We have engineered and deployed an Iridium Satellite Communications device to be utilized as a GPS Tracking & Asset Management solution for the Shipping & Logistics Industry.
- Iridium Satellite Communications Airtime Service Provider

• Whenever Communications, LLC.

(December 2011- February 2013)

- Sales Manager, Aerospace Project Manager, U.S. Government GSA Contract Specialist
- Researched, Responded and Developed Proposals for Government RFI and RFP
- Researched and directed Aerospace SATCOM Solutions and Projects
- Managed Trade-Show Booths, Conference Agendas and participated in business development activities.
- Assisted with Inside & Outside B2B and B2C sales initiatives

Education:

• Georgia Tech - Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp

(Oct 2021 - Present)

• Embry Riddle Aeronautical University – Worldwide

(2010 - 2011)

- Aviation Administration and Business Management
 - ERAU Dean's List Fall, 2010
- Western Michigan University: College of Aviation

(2007-Transfer to ERAU in 2010)

- Aviation Flight Science and Administration
- Plainwell High School
 - Graduated 2007 with High School Diploma

Interests, Skills and Hobbies:

Licensed Private Pilot SEL: 100+ hours PIC. Community Volunteering, Rock Climbing, Snowboarding, Kayaking, Fishing. Read/Write/Speak Conversational French,, HTML, CSS, JS, Node.JS, MongoDB, MySQL, NoSQL, Handlebars, MVC, React, Kotlin, Swift, Kanban.